Russell Carpenter Papers MS041
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, audio and visual material, 1833 -- 2012; 1934 -- 1979; MS041.005; 4.05 Linear Feet; 5 Audiovisual Object(s); 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1882 -- 1957; MS041.005.014
    - Photos: Russell Carpenter, Class of 1924, Leonard Carmichael, MS041.005.014.00011 (Box 14)
    - [Photographs, Jumbo, Dana Hall], MS041.005.014.00012 (Box 14)
    - [Photographs, Personal], 1924; MS041.005.014.00013 (Box 14)
    - [Scrapbook, Class of 1924], MS041.005.014.00014 (Box 14)
    - Theta Delta Chi House, MS041.005.014.00015 (Box 14)
    - Tufts 1939 and World's Fair [Alumni Day], MS041.005.014.00016 (Box 14)
    - Tufts College [Stereoscope Photographs], MS041.005.014.00017 (Box 14)
    - Tufts [Cousens] Gym, September 1931 [Negatives], MS041.005.014.00018 (Box 14)
    - Tufts and Commencement [Negatives], 1925; MS041.005.014.00019 (Box 14)
    - [Tufts Scenes, Negatives], MS041.005.014.00020 (Box 14)
    - Theta Delta Chi [Negatives], 1931; MS041.005.014.00021 (Box 14)
    - Tufts and Whatnots [Construction of Cousens Gym], MS041.005.014.00022 (Box 14)
    - Boston and Fitchburg Railroad Station [Slides], MS041.005.014.00023 (Box 14)
    - [Russell L. Carpenter at P.T. Barnum's Desk], 1955; MS041.005.014.00024 (Box 14)
      photographic print
    - "Jumbo Saving the Clown Elephant", MS041.005.014.00025 (Box 14)
    - [Jumbo being fed by a Policeman], 1882; MS041.005.014.00026 (Box 14)
    - [Caricature of Jumbo and P.T. Barnum titled "Mutual Admiration"], 1882-04-15; MS041.005.014.00027 (Box 14)
      Below the image is written "Mutual Admiration. Barnum to Jumbo. 'You are a humbug after my own heart. You have even beat me in advertising.' Cartoon by Thomas Nast in 'Harper's Weekly,' April 15, 1882."
    - [Jumbo Advertisement for Clark's Trade Mark O.N.T. Spool Cotton], MS041.005.014.00028 (Box 14)
      Also on advertisement is written "Jumbo at Cooney Island" and "Buck and Bindner Bith. 65 Warren St. N.Y."
      Advertisements; Elephants; photographic print; Jumbo
    - [Man in top Hat with an Elephant], MS041.005.014.00029 (Box 14)
      The elephant in the image may be the clown elephant Jumbo saved or Jumbo himself when he was a baby.
      Elephants; photographic print
    - [Portrait of an Unidentified Man], MS041.005.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Lantern slides - Class of 1924, Jumbo, 1934 -- 1954; MS041.005.015.001 (Box 15)
    lantern slide
  - Lantern slides - Class of 1924 - at Tufts, as Alumni, 1920 -- 1954; MS041.005.016.001 (Box 16)
  - "Mutual Admiration" Illustration of P.T. Barnum and Jumbo, MS041.005.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - "Barnum was right!" text, MS041.005.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - "The Showman and the Vestrymen" "Barnum Parleys with the Irate Representatives of St. Pauls" Illustration, MS041.005.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Prize Ticket signed P.T. Barnum, MS041.005.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Men with horse and carriage photo, MS041.005.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Madison Sq. Garden "The famous P.T. Barnum opened here in 1873" photo, MS041.005.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Jenny Lind's music, MS041.005.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - "Burning of the Winter Quarters [of P.T. Barnum] at Bridgeport on Nov. 20, 1887" illustration, MS041.005.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Jumbo rescuing Tom Thumb on train tracks, MS041.005.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - "The Marriage of General Tom Thumb" Photo, MS041.005.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - "Interior of Castle Garden: the first appearance of Jenny Lind in America", MS041.005.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Jenny Lind photo, MS041.005.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Jenny Lind's music, MS041.005.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - Letter from Henry A. Ward "Have you seen the new Jumbo catalogue?...", MS041.005.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - P.T. Barnum's Illustrated News, MS041.005.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - Banquet to Welcom Mr. P.T. Barnum to England Guest Seating card, MS041.005.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - "Poor old Jumbo", MS041.005.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - Polishing stuffed Jumbo's trunk photo, MS041.005.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - Eaton Library and Uprooted tree from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - Ballou Hall, fallen trees from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - Looking up Packard Ave: fallen trees Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Fallen tree on Lew Manley's house on Packard Ave from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - The walk to Ballou, fallen trees, from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - Temporary repairs on the chapel roof from Hurricane of 1938 photo, 1909 -- 1938; MS041.005.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - Fallen trees next to Chapel from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - Fallen trees around East Hall - taken from near Chapel from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - East Hall holding up a fallen elm tree from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - Elm in front of East Hall held up with rope, taken in Nov, from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - Fallen tree in front of Braker Hall from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - Fallen trees from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - Fallen poplars along College Ave from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00031 (Box 17)
  - The fallen poplar trees along College Ave from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00032 (Box 17)
  - Only 3 battered poplar trees left standing on College Ave from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00033 (Box 17)
  - Fallen maple trees on Latin Way, next to Metcalf from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00034 (Box 17)
  - "Pop" Houston's house on Talbot Ave with Fallen Trees from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00035 (Box 17)
  - Steam shovel and winch setting trees upright from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00036 (Box 17)
  - Guy wires on tree in front of chapel from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00037 (Box 17)
  - Fallen trees along College Ave, men walking down path from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00038 (Box 17)
  - Fallen telephone pole looking up Professor's Row from Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00039 (Box 17)
  - "Warning: this tree unsafe" Gifford House in bkgd Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00040 (Box 17)
  - Freshmen cleaning up slate blown from Chapel roof Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00041 (Box 17)
  - Removing fallen trees in front of East Hall Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00042 (Box 17)
  - Behind chapel, fallen trees chopped up for removal Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00043 (Box 17)
  - Tree removal Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00044 (Box 17)
  - Fallen trees in front of Ballou Hurricane of 1938 photo, MS041.005.017.00045 (Box 17)
  - Advertisement for Jumbo Excursions, MS041.005.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Explanation of Jumbo's Manikin, MS041.005.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - Spool Cotton Ad with Jumbo, MS041.005.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - "Jumbo at Coney Island" Clark's Spool Cotton Ad, MS041.005.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Jumbo, Baby Elephant and Tom Thumb Waiting for Train, MS041.005.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - Jumbo Saving the Clown Elephant, MS041.005.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - Jumbo Saving Elephant from Train, MS041.005.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - Dead Jumbo after the Accident, MS041.005.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - Scenes from P.T. Barnum's Life, MS041.005.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - Girls with Stuffed Jumbo's Legs, MS041.005.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - "P.T. Barnum's Greatest Show on Earth" Ad, MS041.005.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - "The Book of Jumbo: History of the Largest Elephant that ever lived", MS041.005.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - Carriage driving under Jumbo, MS041.005.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - "Jumbo goes back to Europe" Ad, MS041.005.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - Jumbo carrying people, MS041.005.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - "Jumbo at Coney Island" Clark's Spool Cotton Ad, MS041.005.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - Part of First Page of Barnum's "Herald of Freedom and Gospel Witness" for Aug 21, 1833; MS041.005.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - Jumbo in Crate returning to USA, MS041.005.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - Jenny Lind Photo, MS041.005.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - Jumbo with sign "Barnum and Jumbo's ABC", MS041.005.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - Directions for preservation of marine animals, part two, signed PT Barnum Sept 20, 1886; MS041.005.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - Directions for preservation of marine animals, part one, MS041.005.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - "Jumbo in Chains" photo and cablegram ordering Barnum to buy Jumbo, MS041.005.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - Jenny Lind Photo, MS041.005.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Photo of Julius Benedict, Good Friend of PT Barnum, MS041.005.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - Students looking at stuffed Jumbo, MS041.005.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - Children looking at stuffed Jumbo, MS041.005.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - Photo of PT Barnum, MS041.005.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - Man Cleaning Stuffed Jumbo's Foot, MS041.005.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - Photo of PT Barnum and Child, MS041.005.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - Letter from Henry A. Ward stipulating Jumbo's skin be sent to Tufts dated Aug 29, 1885; MS041.005.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - Jumbo's skeleton, MS041.005.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - Jumbo being hit by train, MS041.005.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - Letter to Prof. Marshall explaining the division of Jumbo post-mortem dated 4 Sept, 1885; MS041.005.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - Card to PT Barnum from Julius Benedict dated 10 April, 1874; MS041.005.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - Advertisement for Willimantic Thread with Jumbo, MS041.005.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - Photos of Jumbo in crate arriving in USA, MS041.005.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - "The Only Living Hippopotamus..." Advertisement, MS041.005.018.00038 (Box 18)
  - "The Fejee Mermaid" Photo, MS041.005.018.00039 (Box 18)
  - Photo of Julius Benedict, MS041.005.018.00040 (Box 18)
  - Ad about snakes for Barnum's Show, MS041.005.018.00041 (Box 18)
  - Photo of Jumbo not wanting to leave London Zoo, MS041.005.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - Photo of elephants and people on bridge, MS041.005.018.00043 (Box 18)
  - Photo of Jumbo being fed, MS041.005.018.00044 (Box 18)
  - "Jumbo at the bar" Ad for Clark's Spool Cotton, MS041.005.018.00045 (Box 18)
  - "Jumbo at the opera" Ad for Clark's Spool Cotton, MS041.005.018.00046 (Box 18)
  - "Jumbo's Arrival" Ad for Clark's Spool Cotton, MS041.005.018.00047 (Box 18)
  - Jenny Lind Photo, MS041.005.018.00048 (Box 18)
  - Barnum's Great Show Toy Book, MS041.005.018.00049 (Box 18)
  - "J is for Jumbo..." page from book, MS041.005.018.00050 (Box 18)
  - Jumbo talk, 1985; MS041.005.019.00001 (Case 19)
    audiocassettes
  - Jumbo talk (copy), 1985; MS041.005.019.00002 (Case 19)
  - 1924 reunions, 1939; MS041.005.020.00001 (Reel 20)
    35 mm film section as well.
    16mm
  - 1924 reunions, reel #1, 1929 -- 1934; MS041.005.020.00002 (Reel 20)
  - Tufts 1924 reunions, reel #2, 1939 -- 1964; MS041.005.020.00003 (Reel 20)
  - Ballou Hall, Barnum, Barnum desk, Jumbo and R.L.C, MS041.005.020.00004 (Reel 20)
  - Construction of Dana wing, 1963; MS041.005.020.00005 (Reel 20)
  - Jumbo, R. L. C. and people, MS041.005.020.00006 (Reel 20)
  - Tufts football game, Leo Lewis briefly, MS041.005.020.00007 (Reel 20)
  - Rabbit Movie, MS041.005.020.00008 (Reel 20)
  - Barnum talk, 1985; MS041.005.021.00001 (Case 21)
  - Barnum talk (copy), 1985; MS041.005.021.00003 (Case 21)
  - Tufts Christmas party, [Lambert-Kingsley show], 1953; MS041.005.022.00001 (Case 22)
  - Letter from Barnum about Jumbo in the Museum, 1803 -- 1889; MS041.005.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - Letter from Barnum about Jumbo in the Museum, 1803 -- 1889; MS041.005.023.00002 (Box 23)
  - Thank You Letter from PT Barnum to Prof Marshall, 1806 -- 1886; MS041.005.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - Letter from Barnum to Prof Marshall, 1886; MS041.005.023.00004 (Box 23)
  - Letter to Prof Marshall from Henry Ward about the skining of Jumbo, 1885; MS041.005.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - Photo of dead Jumbo, MS041.005.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - Dictionary entry for "Jumbo", MS041.005.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - Uses of "Jumbo" in products, MS041.005.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - Jumbo on seal with alphabet, MS041.005.023.00009 (Box 23)
  - Cover of book "Jumbo March" by V.D. Dygert, MS041.005.023.00010 (Box 23)
  - "Jumbo goes back to Europe" Advertisement, MS041.005.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - "A Suggested Change in the British Coat of Arms" Picture, MS041.005.023.00012 (Box 23)
  - Photo of Jumbo carrying people, MS041.005.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - Drawing of Small Elephant and Man, MS041.005.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - Picture of PT Barnum, MS041.005.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - "Winter Quarters in Bridgeport", 1889; MS041.005.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - Photo of James A Baily, MS041.005.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - Picture of Building, MS041.005.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - Ad for The Hippotheatron and New York Cirque, MS041.005.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - Ad for elephants in Circus, MS041.005.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - Photo of Barnum's Circus Train, 1876; MS041.005.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - "The Ruins of the New American Museum..." Photo, 1868; MS041.005.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - "Capturing White Whales in the St Lawrence River, for Shipment to the American Museum" Drawing, 1869; MS041.005.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - Print of "Burning of the American Museum" July 13, 1864; MS041.005.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - Copy of Cover of Barnum's Autobiography, MS041.005.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - Dedication Page from Barnum's Autobiography, 1854; MS041.005.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - Title Page of Barnum's Autobiography, MS041.005.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - Print from Engraving of Barnum, MS041.005.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - List of Receipts for Jenny Lind's Concerts, MS041.005.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - Ad for Jenny Lind's Last Concert, 1851; MS041.005.023.00030 (Box 23)
  - Ad for Ossian's Serenade, MS041.005.023.00031 (Box 23)
  - Ticket for Jenny Lind's First Grand Concert, 1806 -- 1851; MS041.005.023.00032 (Box 23)
  - Print of "Castle Garden in 1850", MS041.005.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - Print of Jenny Lind's Arrival in USA, MS041.005.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - Photo of Jenny Lind, MS041.005.023.00035 (Box 23)
  - Print of "Iranistan", 1869; MS041.005.023.00036 (Box 23)
  - Print of Elephant pulling plow, MS041.005.023.00037 (Box 23)
  - "Grand Entrance of the Asiatic Caravan, Museum and Menagerie of PT Barnum", MS041.005.023.00038 (Box 23)
  - "General Tom Thumb..." Photo, MS041.005.023.00039 (Box 23)
  - Print from engraving of General Tom Thumb, 1844; MS041.005.023.00040 (Box 23)
  - Drawing of "The Fejee Mermaid", MS041.005.023.00041 (Box 23)
  - Print of "A Barnum 'Mermaid Cut'", MS041.005.023.00042 (Box 23)
  - Print of "Barnum's American Museum", MS041.005.023.00043 (Box 23)
  - Print of Small Building with "Oysters" sign, MS041.005.023.00044 (Box 23)
  - Bridgeport Centenial Coin of Barnum, MS041.005.023.00045 (Box 23)
  - Envelope Addressed to Barnum, MS041.005.023.00046 (Box 23)
  - Picture of Statue of Barnum, MS041.005.023.00047 (Box 23)
  - Ad for Barnum's Company, MS041.005.023.00048 (Box 23)
  - "There's another sucker born every minute", MS041.005.023.00049 (Box 23)
  - "hum-bug" A contemporary caricature, MS041.005.023.00050 (Box 23)
  - Barnum's Roman Hippodrome, 1874; MS041.005.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - Letter from Barnum, 1803 -- 1889; MS041.005.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - Postal Markings, MS041.005.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - Lithograph of Jenny Lind, MS041.005.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - "Squales and Beezes", MS041.005.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - "Barnum's American Museum", MS041.005.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - "Elephantine Agriculture", MS041.005.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - "The Fejee Mermaid", MS041.005.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - "Squalls and Breezes", MS041.005.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - "Manager Barnum and Four Famous Midgets", MS041.005.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - "New York's Welcome to Jenny Lind", MS041.005.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - Dedication "to my wife and family...", MS041.005.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - Photo of Dead Jumbo, MS041.005.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - Letter from PT Barnum about Barnum Hall, MS041.005.024.00014 (Box 24)
  - Advertisement of Jumbo from Barnum's pamphlet "The Art of Money-Getting", 1882; MS041.005.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - Letter from PT Barnum to Prof Marshall about visiting Prof Ward, MS041.005.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - Photo of Science Classroom, MS041.005.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - Photo of Man examining bust of Barnum, MS041.005.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - Advertisement that Jumbo is coming, MS041.005.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - Photo of Jumbo in cage being pulled through street, MS041.005.024.00020 (Box 24)
  - Ad for Barnum's Circus and Jumbo, MS041.005.024.00021 (Box 24)
  - Ad for Jumbo, MS041.005.024.00022 (Box 24)
  - Private Letter from Barnum, 1887; MS041.005.024.00023 (Box 24)
  - Photo of PT Barnum, 1874; MS041.005.024.00024 (Box 24)
  - Students in room with stuffed Barnum, MS041.005.024.00025 (Box 24)
  - Letter from Barnum to Prof. Marshall, MS041.005.024.00026 (Box 24)
  - Print of "My Birthplace", MS041.005.024.00027 (Box 24)
  - Color Print of "The Fejee Mermaid", MS041.005.024.00028 (Box 24)
    Fiji; Mermaids; lantern slide
  - Copy of programme of Jenny Lind's performance 11 Sept, 1850; MS041.005.024.00029 (Box 24)
  - Letter from Henry Ward to Prof. Marshall about getting Jumbo to Tufts, MS041.005.024.00030 (Box 24)
  - Certification by Barnum of Deposit of baby Elephant with Fairfield County Historical Society, MS041.005.024.00031 (Box 24)
  - Western Union Telegraph to John Marshall from Barnum and Baily about arrival of Jumbo at Tufts, MS041.005.024.00032 (Box 24)
  - Photo of Barnum, 1882; MS041.005.024.00033 (Box 24)
  - Memorial of Jumbo, MS041.005.024.00034 (Box 24)
  - Children looking at stuffed Jumbo, MS041.005.024.00035 (Box 24)
  - Students with stuffed Jumbo, MS041.005.024.00036 (Box 24)
  - Girls reading with stuffed Jumbo, MS041.005.024.00037 (Box 24)
  - Letter from Barnum to Prof Marshall May 8, 1896; MS041.005.024.00038 (Box 24)
  - Letter from Barnum to Prof Marshall March 26, 1870; MS041.005.024.00039 (Box 24)
  - Photo of Stuffed Jumbo, MS041.005.024.00040 (Box 24)
  - Letter from PT Barnum to Prof Marshall Dec 19, 1889; MS041.005.024.00041 (Box 24)
  - Drawing of old PT Barnum, MS041.005.024.00042 (Box 24)
  - "The Man of the World" Picture of Barnum, MS041.005.024.00043 (Box 24)
  - Program from Welcome Banquet for Barnum, MS041.005.024.00044 (Box 24)
  - Place setting for Banquet to welcome Barnum, MS041.005.024.00045 (Box 24)
  - Letter from Barnum to Prof Marshall April 6, 1889; MS041.005.024.00046 (Box 24)
  - Photo of Stuffed Jumbo and Stuffed Baby Elephant, MS041.005.024.00047 (Box 24)
  - Stuffed Jumbo and Man, MS041.005.024.00048 (Box 24)
  - Photo of stuffed Jumbo being moved by horse-drawn cart, MS041.005.024.00049 (Box 24)
  - Lantern Slides, 1940; MS041.005.025.00001 (Box 25)
    Students; Professors; Buildings; Jumbo; Tufts University; Tufts College
  - Disassembled Lantern Slides, 1940; MS041.005.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - A Reception and Dinner Invitation to Honor President and Mrs. Leonard Carmichael, December 9, 1952, MS041.005.025.00003 (Box 25)
    The invitation was located amongst the lantern slides. Dr. Russell Carpenter was the toastmaster at the farewell reception given for President Leonard Carpenter who was leaving Tufts to work at the Smithsonian Institute.
    Dinners and Dining; Reception; Carmichael, Pearl; Carmichael, Leonard; Carpenter, Russell L.
  - P.T. Barnum and Jumbo Audiocassettes, MS041.005.025.00004 (Box 25)
    Lectures or lecturing; audiocassette; Jumbo; Carpenter, Russell L.; Barnum, P. T. (Phineas Taylor)
  - Slides for Dr. Carpenter's lectures on P.T. Barnum and Jumbo, 1940; MS041.005.025.00005 (Box 25)
    Students; Professors; Buildings; Jumbo
  - VHS Tape: Remarks made by Russell L. Carpenter on the occasion of the reception announcing the establishment of the Russell L. Carpenter Fund for teaching and research in biology, 1987-11-18; MS041.005.026.00001 (Box 26)
    videocassette